[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Forrest Gump, Forrest joins the U.S. Army and becomes best friends with Benjamin Buford Blue (played by Mykelti Williamson). What was Benjamins nickname?", "correct_answer": "Bubba", "incorrect_answers": ["Beau", "Billy", "Bennie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of sounds do baby chinchillas produce in order to show their parents that they are hungry?", "correct_answer": "Chirps", "incorrect_answers": ["Hissing", "Barks", "Clucking"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During WWII, Einstein was paid $25 per day for his consultation on the Manhattan Project.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Napoleons favorite animal to draw from the comedy hit Napoleon Dynamite?", "correct_answer": "a liger (a lion and tiger mix )", "incorrect_answers": ["a unicorn", "a T-Rex", "a dragon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the first  TV show to demand and get $1 million per minute for ads.", "correct_answer": "Seinfeld", "incorrect_answers": ["Everyone Loves Raymond", "Frasier", "Saturday Night Live"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In several scenes of the Bourne movies Bourne is shown to be adept at fighting using sticks, batons, and bats. Which combat system teaches this skill?", "correct_answer": "Escrima", "incorrect_answers": ["Muay Ti", "LoFan", "ChiYung"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before he was offered the Indians managerial job in the film major League, Lou was a former manager for what minor league team?", "correct_answer": "Toledo Mud Hens", "incorrect_answers": ["Columbus Clippers", "Peoria Chiefs", "Lansing Lugnuts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2002 movie was Kim Wayans in?", "correct_answer": "Juwanna Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Snow Dogs", "Spiderman", "Titanic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A book claiming that the story of Wilhelm Tell was just a myth was burned at the stake in Switzerland.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays Carter in the Disney movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "Selena Gomez", "incorrect_answers": ["Jason Earles", "Demi Lovato", "Jason Dolly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the USA, what is the longest month?", "correct_answer": "October", "incorrect_answers": ["August", "January", "April"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The master bedroom should be as far away from the front door as possible.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]